reship.com 2015-06-07

# Privacy Policy

**Reship Privacy Policy  
**

**INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE  
**

This privacy policy applies to [http://www.reship.com](http://www.reship.com/)  owned and operated by Monark Media Ventures (“Reship”). This privacy policy describes how Reship collects and uses the personal information you provide on our web site: [http://www.reship.com](http://www.reship.com/) . It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.   

**Collection and Use of Personal Information  
**

We collect the following personal information from you: 

·        Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number 

·        Billing Information such as credit card number 

·        Unique Identifiers such as user name, password 

We use this information to:   

•       Fulfill your order 

•       Send you an order confirmation 

•       Send product updates or warranty information 

•       Respond to customer service requests 

•       Administer your account 

•       Send you a newsletter 

•       Send you marketing communications 

•       Respond to your questions and concerns 

**Choice/Opt-Out**

•       You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails   

**Information Sharing  
**

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. We do not sell your personal information to third parties. We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as mail-outs.Such companies are authorized to use your personal information _only as necessary to provide_ these services to us.   

We may also disclose your personal information   

• As required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process 

• when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights,protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request, 

•If Reship.com is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information, to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.   

We make your contact information available to other users that you transact with on this site to help complete the transaction.   

**Checkout  
**

If finalize and pay for your order, you will provide your credit card number, we  may use cookies, for example, to keep track of your preferences and profile information. Cookies are also used to collect general usage and volume statistical information that does not include personal information. We use another company to place cookies on your computer to collect non-personal information to compile aggregated statistics for us about visitors to our site. 

**Web beacons  
**

Our Web pages contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) and are used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used and may be used in some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns.

**Analytics /Log Files  
**

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system,date/time stamp, and click stream data. 

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. 

We do link IP addresses automatically-collected data to personal information. IP addresses are tied to personal information to increase the security of the customer,ensuring there is no unauthorized access to a customer’s account.   

**Behavioral Targeting / Re-Targeting  
**

We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personal information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking here. Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.   

**Links to Other Web Sites  
**

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Reship.com. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit.   

**Social Media Features and Widgets  
**

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook and Twitter button. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site,and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.   

**Security  
**

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission 

and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site,you can contact us at techsupport@Reship.com. We provide two means for you to make a purchase on our site. You can either use our order form or a third party payment option. If you use our shopping cart, the transmission of sensitive information collected on our order form is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL). If you choose to use a third party payment option to pay for your order, its privacy policy and security practices will apply to your information. We encourage you to read that privacy policy before providing your information.   

**Updating/Accessing/Amending/Correcting Personal Information  
**

If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, amend, delete/remove or deactivate it by making the change on our member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at info@Reship.comor by contacting us by email at the contact information listed below.   

**Email:**

**Data Retention:** We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at info@Reship.com. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.   

**Notification of Privacy Policy Changes  
**

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.   

**Contact Information  
**

You can contact us by writing or emailing us at the address below:   

Email:                    [info@reship.com](mailto:info@reship.com)

Mail:                       3820 NE Airport Way,Portland, Oregon 97230.
